Hey... Fudo.
Yeah?
Do you think... maybe...
Hey, look at that!
I b-baked the cookies this morning.
I don't know if you'll like them, but...
They're shockingly delicious!
Really?
I'm so glad.
Fudo? What's the matter?
Just...
On a day with the perfect date weather,
eating sweet things made by
the person I love the most...
Desumi-san...
I'm the luckiest man in the universe.
You just love to exaggerate.
Ah, Desumi-san...
You are beautiful.
I could look at you for hours.
Stare...
C'mon, don't stare!
You're not even blinking!
But don't get the wrong idea!
It's not that I don't like it.
I'm just not... used to it.
Oh so cute...
Desumi-san...
I have a serious favor to ask you.
A favor?
According to the specialist
texts I consulted on the topic,
couples are supposed to hold hands.
Do you think we could try it?
H-Hold hands? Us?
I can't do it!
It's just too soon for us!
Desumi-san!
I said I can't do it!
But...
T-Think about it, Fudo!
This is only our third-ever date!
It's premature!
Statistics suggest that hand-holding tends
to happen on the second or third date!
The average couple is incredible!
You okay up here, Red?!
Allow me to explain!
Freezing Sentai Gelato 5
Freezing Sentai Gelato
5's leader, Red Gelato,
Aikawa
Fudo
a.k.a. Fudo Aikawa...
Secret Society Gekko
and leader of combatants
for Secret Society Gekko,
the Reaper Princess, a.k.a. Desumi Magahara...
Desumi Magahara
have climbed the insurmountable wall
that stands between their organizations
to engage in a taboo relationship!
Episode 1    I Love You!
What an intense battle!
I don't think there's
anything I can do to help.
I'm leaving this to you, Red!
Desumi-san...
We're holding hands right now.
Y-You mean... we did it?
We did!
Isn't it wonderful, Fudo?
And doing it with interlocked
fingers like we did
is apparently a very advanced act!
It's a day worth remembering—
the first time we held hands.
Desumi-san...
My first-ever girlfriend.
1 Week
Earlier
I'm so glad I worked up my courage that day!
Hero Sentai
Gelato 5 Headquarters
Red Gelato
Fudo Aikawa
Good morning, Fudo-senpai!
Hey. Morning, Haru-kun.
Pink Gelato
Haru Arisugawa
You can use this, if you like.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
It's nothing, really.
But I guess it's almost time
for the meeting, right?
Want to walk there together?
Refreshing!
Goes down easy!
For building ideal muscles
Protein 98.5%
The Rich Flavor
100% Real Milk
Delicious Milk
Sure thing.
C'mon, don't be shy!
A date with me is all
the excitement you need!
Actually... I'm rather busy...
Hayato-san's at it again.
Blue Gelato
Hayato Ojino
Where should we go?
Karaoke? A club?
Excuse me, I have to...
Just don't fall in love too fast
when you see me on the dance floor!
Just leave it all to me.
Hey!
Providing a cool escort for
an adorable little kitten
is my form of justi—
She knows she wants me.
Look at you, right on time!
Yellow Gelato
Misaki Jinguji
Green Gelato
Daigo Todoroki
It seems we're all here.
All right!
Good morning, Gelato 5!
Gelato 5 Commander
Professor Big Gelato
Good morning, sir!
Morning!
Mornin'!
Good morning!
Professor, the package you requested.
It's appreciated as always, Daigo-kun.
What a fine smell!
Croissants!
Hey, can I have some too?
Of course you can!
Feel free to help yourselves while I talk!
Reaper Princess...
A powerful Gekko combatant who began
appearing roughly six months ago.
As you all know, Gekko is a secret
society plotting world domination.
But the appearance of the Reaper Princess has
made them more formidable than ever.
I want you all to engage her with caution!
Secret Society Gekko appearance detected.
Gelato 5, move out at once.
Gelato 5, move out!
Help!
Princess Series
Reaper Princess
Gekko Monster
Culverin Bear
Moonlight
Soldiers
Cower in fear, pathetic humans!
It's Gekko!
Man, Culverin Bear is huge!
That's enough of that!
There you are!
They're here!
Freezing Change!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Change Gelato!
The aroma of strawberry,
the flavor of justice!
Red Gelato!
The aroma of soda, the flavor of courage!
Blue Gelato!
The aroma of lemon, the flavor of life!
Yellow Gelato!
The aroma of peach, the flavor of love!
Pink Gelato!
The aroma of pistachio, the flavor of peace!
Green Gelato!
Together, we are...
Freezing Sentai Gelato 5!
Underestimate us on pain of fire!
We'll have our revenge at last!
Get them!
Sweet Berry Impact!
Megaton Lemon Crush!
Sky Peach Rain!
Vacuum Pistachio Strike!
Twin Soda Slash!
Heroes rock!
Impressive as ever, Gelato 5!
But the rest won't be so easy!
The rest of you, handle Culverin Bear!
I'll take the Reaper Princess!
Let's go!
Right!
Retreat!
Let's call it off for now!
B-But I'll get you next time!
I've never met someone who
could keep up with me before.
Perhaps this is what they call destiny.
We'll meet again... Red Gelato.
Lick, lick...
Fighting in the morning,
training in the afternoon?
He's a role model for all heroes
with a work ethic like that.
What's going on in your life, boy?
Don't you do anything but bodybuilding?
There's something on my mind.
Oh?
Knowing Fudo-kun,
he's probably mulling over issues of world
peace, or perhaps the nature of justice.
I was thinking about the woman I love.
What?!
F-Fudo-kun!
Y-You've developed a crush?!
It was love at first sight.
I've never been in love before now!
H-Have you told her how you feel?
Of course not.
I'm a hero.
She and I live in two different wo—
Fool!
P-Professor?
What's there to say a
hero can't fall in love?
You're as human as the rest of us!
You must tell her how you feel at once!
But...
That's an order!
Are you sure, Professor?!
Love will bring you to the
next stage of your life!
I'll take responsibility
for whatever happens!
Very well, sir!
I'm off!
I always thought his single-minded
focus on bodybuilding was sad,
but it's good to see he's
a red-blooded young man!
But what kind of woman could it
be, who's stolen Fudo-kun's heart?
Could it be a nurse, perhaps?
I've a fondness for nurses myself!
I was surprised by your invitation
to this little tête-à-tête, Red.
But you don't have to explain...
You want to pick up where we left off, right?
I was hoping to settle things myself!
What is it?
I love you!
Wha?
Clink...
Love After World Domination!
I love you!
From the moment we first met...
I've loved you!
I just wanted to tell you—
Now hang on a second!
Are you nuts?
We're mortal enemies, remember?!
I'm perfectly sane!
Did you hit your head somewhere?
Don't worry.
I got Professor Big Gelato's permission.
Exactly, there's no way he'd permit—
What?!
Of course... I see your game now.
You know I've had no experience with such
things... and you're teasing me about it.
How humiliating!
Squee...
squee
Using that as a pretext
to throw me off my game...
I'm disappointed in you, Red!
No, I swear—
You'll pay for this, fiend!
It's not like that, Desumi-san!
I haven't given you
permission to use my name!
No man could possibly ever love me!
I'm the kind of woman...
whose comrades spread rumors that
my favorite food is raw bear meat!
It's not! Your favorite foods
are pancakes and pasta!
How would you know that, creep?!
They also say that I drink
the blood of wild boars!
No! You mainly drink green smoothies!
They say I wander the streets at
night seeking strong men to beat up!
At night, you do Pilates!
That I'm an alien killing machine!
You were born...
in Hakata!
How did you know all that?!
Desumi Magahara
1 like
I made mentaiko pasta
#homecooking
#wishIwasbetteratit
Comments
I looked through all your
social media accounts.
Hello there, it looks delicious
And those replies from "Proteinman"...
They're from me.
Hello there, it looks delicious
You're no killing machine.
You always do your nails up in a cute way,
you love your fancy accessories,
and you change up your perfume
based on how you feel that day.
You're as real as a girl can be.
Real girls don't wield flails.
Don't worry. I'll catch it.
B-But we're enemies!
I think we can work it out!
But...
Would you please be my girlfriend?
I-It's not possible—
Desumi-san, I mean this!
Fine.
I... I'm looking forward to it.
B-But just so you know, I don't know
anything about the mechanics of dating!
Don't worry. I don't know, either!
And now...
By the way, Fudo.
When I headed out this morning,
my cat did the funniest—
H-Hang on a minute.
You have a cat, Desumi-san?
Oh? You didn't know?
The great Fudo didn't even know I have a cat!
There's still so much I don't know.
I'll take pity on you,
and give you a special little peek!
Her name's Hellko!
Well? Isn't she a sweetie?
Desumi-san caught herself in the shot!
And it looks like she
just got out of the bath!
Can a man truly feel this much happiness?
Well, I know Hellko's pretty cute,
but you really do love to exaggerate!
It's hardly an exaggeration.
Just being with you really
makes me that happy.
I feel the same way.
But don't forget, Fudo.
We can't let anybody know about us.
Failure of Justice
Daily Hero (Extra)
Reaper Princess Steamy Love Red
Photos of their tryst in the middle of work!
No denial of the reports of their affair
It's true!
A Hero Dethroned!
An unprecedented scandal
Hero
Secret Society
If this comes out, we won't
be able to stay together.
It might even become national news!
I know that.
I'm not much of a secretive person,
but I will keep this secret!
Good.
But some day...
I hope the world becomes a place where
we can see each other, heads held high!
Right, Fudo?
Desumi-san!
I love you!
Red, we're done—
snap
Rumba of the Reaper
Rumba of the Reaper!
Hey!
R-Red, hang in there!
I-Impressive indeed, Reaper Princess!
I'll see that you pay for this...
Let us meet again... soon.
V-Very well!
I'll be ready and waiting!
Farewell, Fudo... Red!
I'll meet you, whenever you dare!
Perhaps the day after tomorrow?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Allow me to explain!
This is the story of a hero of justice
and a secret society's combatant
beginning their journey down
the road of forbidden love!
Preview
Training again? A true inspiration!
By the way, Fudo-kun...
Speaking as the one who
pushed you to go for it,
I was wondering... How'd the confession go?
Oh? Maybe he's not listening?
Fudo-kun?!
Next time on Love After World Domination:
Episode 2     The Truth About Dating
Episode 2: "The Truth About Dating"!